It coincides with Daqin,
يتزامن مع دقين ،
Beiqi,
Beiqi ،
The three states of Nanzhao stand together
تقف ولايات Nanzhao الثلاث معًا
and Daqin State is prosperous.
وولاية داقين مزدهرة.
State Preceptor Lin Weixu took office less than a month ago,
تولى مدير الدولة لين ويكسو منصبه منذ أقل من شهر ،
and took down Nanzhao State in one fell swoop,
وأزالوا ولاية نانتشاو بضربة واحدة ،
plotting unparalleled in the world.
تآمر لا مثيل لها في العالم.
The whole court is very afraid of him.
المحكمة كلها تخاف منه جدا.
You little merman,
أنت حوري البحر الصغير ،
Nanzhao has died.
لقد مات Nanzhao.
Just surrender.
فقط استسلم.
For us to enjoy.
بالنسبة لنا للاستمتاع.
You want to run away?
تريد أن تهرب؟
Beat him!
اضربه!
Darn it. Aren't
رتقها.  لا
all the captives of Nanzhao locked up in prison?
كل أسرى Nanzhao المسجونين في السجن؟
How did he escape?
كيف هرب؟
Beat him,
اضربه،
Stop!
قف!
The person I asked you
الشخص الذي سألتك
to run to Supreme Court is really not something,
الترشح للمحكمة العليا ليس شيئًا حقًا ،
You tortured him like this.
لقد عذبته هكذا.
Where did you get that silly girl?
من أين حصلت على تلك الفتاة السخيفة؟
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
Beat him!
اضربه!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
How dare you attack Supreme Court?
كيف تجرؤ على مهاجمة المحكمة العليا؟
State Preceptor's Mansion,
قصر مدير الدولة ،
Lin Weixu.
لين ويكسو.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Master.
يتقن.
Sir.
سيد.
This guy has been standing at the door.
كان هذا الرجل يقف عند الباب.
Why can't I drive him away?
لماذا لا أستطيع إبعاده؟
It seems that he followed us secretly.
يبدو أنه تبعنا في الخفاء.
You.
أنت.
It's cute.
انه ظريف.
Let him stay in the mansion.
دعه يبقى في القصر.
Are you willing to do that?
هل انت سوف تفعل ذلك؟
I said,
انا قلت،
are you willing to do it?
هل انت على استعداد لفعل ذلك؟
Take him down to wash and change clothes.
أنزله لغسل الملابس وتغييرها.
Yes.
نعم.
Your Excellency,
امتيازك،
it's ready.
إنه جاهز.
This merman
هذا الحوري
is so handsome.
وسيم جدا.